Thorton Hall 912, 1600 Holloway Ave, San Francisco, CA 94132. $+1 \ (415) \ 767-8984$

m.cadier.kim@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a researcher in combinatorial optimization and machine learning. On the application side, I work on image processing methods and neural network architectures for medical data. As a mathematician, I am interested in a class of polytopes related to classical root systems and submodular set functions. More broadly I am interested in combinatorics and discrete geometry. With experience in both professional software development and pure math research, I have an adaptive skill set combining scientific rigour and application-minded heuristics.

test

EDUCATION

SFSU: M.A. in Mathematics, 2015 (in progress)

Advisor: Dr. Federico Ardila.

Thesis: The Geometry of Generalized W Permutohedra

SFSU: B.A. Mathematics, Philosophy, Computer Science, May 2012

AWARDS

Maxwell Scholarship, College of Science and Engineering, SFSU, \$4,000, 2013-14. $(CM)^2$ grant, Department of Mathematics, SFSU, \$5,000, 2012-2013.

Papers

A Neural Network Architecture for Detecting Trachoma Infection on Everted Eyelids with Dr. Travis Porco (UCSF) and Dr. Kazunori Okada.

A Characterization of Generalized Permutohedra of the Classical Reflection Groups

with David Arcila and Julián Romero, 2015

WORK HISTORY

Visiting Researcher

UCSF: UCSF The Francis I. Proctor

Foundation

San Francisco, CA

May, 2015 - December 2015

Research and develop a novel artificial vision algorithm to detect the presence of follicles on images of everted eyelids using a convolutional neural networks. Additionally I work on an image processing pipeline to label, segment and preprocess the images coming from the field.

Data Science Associate

Argyle Data

San Mateo, CA

June, 2014 - February, 2015

I worked alongside the senior software engineer to research, prototype, and develop machine learning and statistical algorithms for fraud detection.

Graduate Teaching Assistant

SFSU

San Francisco, CA

September 2012 - December 2014

Taught undergraduate algebra, precalculus and calculus courses.

SELECTED PROJECTS

- Researching, implementing, and testing hidden Markov models for fraud detection in a telecommunications network. This involved extensive exploration, querying, and munging of network packet data.
- Adapted and implemented a counting Bloom filter design from an AT&T research paper for Spam detection in SMS traffic.

• Investigating the applicability of a recurrent neural network classifier for use on a set of medical images gathered by researchers at the Francis I Proctor Foundation at UCSF. (in progress)

Programming Languages Java, Python, Matlab, Julia, C/C++, Ruby, Latex

LANGUAGES

English (Native), French (Fluent written and oral)

References

Arshak Navruzyan, VP of Product Management, Argyle Data,

arshak.navruzyan@argyledata.com

Dejan Miljkovic Senior Software Engineer, Argyle Data,

dejan.miljkovic@argyledata.com